Finding aid to the Sophia Smith Collection zines collection SSC.MS.00434
Sophia Smith Collection
- Ugly Mug, #6, Fall/Winter 1996 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Unsupervised Existence, #6, Dec 1991 (Box 17)
- Urban Pantheist, #1, 1998 (Box 17)
- Velvet Grass, #13, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Verbal Abuse, #2, Fall 1993 (Box 17)
- Vigil Anti, #17, 1995 (Box 17)
- Warped Reality, #3Summer 1995; #4, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Way-Sassy, Spring 1997; Autumn 1996 (Box 17)
- We Flood Through, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Weird Flower, #6, 1994 (Box 17)
- What you can Learn from a Glamour Girl, 1995 (Box 17)
- What's Up, #9, Dec/Jan 1998/1999 (Box 17)
- Whipped and Creamed, undated; 1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Whump, #1, Winter 1995/1996 (Box 17)
- Where to?, May 1995 (Box 17)
- Wig Winter 1997; #7, Winter 1998/1999 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Wild Chirp, #1, Fall 1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Wild Honey Pie, #9undated (2 copies); #10, 1995 (Box 17)
- Wingnut, #4, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Wives Tales undated (2 copies) (Box 17)
- WMBR, Fall 1996; Fall 1999 (Box 17)
- Women in the Arts Festival Feb/Mar 1997 (2 copies) (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Women's Alternative Health Care Pamphlet, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Women's Underground Music Directory for NYC, 1994 (2 copies) (Box 18)
- Words and Smiles, #2, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Work Progress! Vol. 1, #1, Apr 1997 (Box 18)
- Wrecking Ball, #2, undated (Box 18)
- Writer's Block, #8, 1991/1992 (Box 18)
- X-Girl Apr. 1994 (2 copies) (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Yakuza, #3Winter 1993; #5undated; #6undated (record enclosed); #8, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- YOB, #1, Apr./May 1996 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- You Might As Well Live…, #1Sept/Oct 1995; #2, Winter 1995/1996 (Box 18)
- Youtalkintame?, #11994; #2 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- You've Never Heard Such Sounds in you Life, #1undated; #2, Sep. 1994 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Zine Silver, undated (Box 18)
- Loose material: letter and mail (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Loose material: one page written pieces (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Loose material: pages from L. Mah to Tinuviel (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Loose material: poetry (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Loose material: extra pages (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Ajuan Mance zines, 2012-2017; 2017-S-0052; Mance, Ajuan Maria
  Scope and Contents
  Several zines created by Ajuan Maria Mance, a professor of African American literature at Mills College, including Gender Studies (2014), Gender Studies: Requiem for a Hot Comb (2015), Gender Studies: Child's Play (2016) and other titles.
  Zines were purchased by the library from the creator's store on Etsy in 2017.
  - Gender Studies, 2014; Mance, Ajuan Maria (Box 19)
  - The Ancestors' Juneteenth, 2017 (Box 19)
  - Gender Studies: Requiem for a Hot Comb, 2015 (Box 19)
  - Gender Studies: Child's Play, 2016 (Box 19)
  - A Blues for Black Santa, 2013 (Box 19)
  - 1001 Black Men: Sports Pages, 2012 (Box 19)
  - 1001 Black Men: Black Nerds, Afro-Geeks, and Dungeon Masters with Soul, 2012 (Box 19)
  - 1001 Black Men: A Gathering of Old Black Men, 2014 (Box 19)
  - A Little Book of Big Black Bears, 2016 (Box 19)
- B&D Press zines, 2009, 2012, 2014; 2018-S-0073; 14 items (14 zines)
  Purchased from B&D Press
  Includes twelve titles from The Life and Times of Butch Dykes, Madame Sata, and Newsgirls
  - The Life and Times of Butch Dykes, 12 titles, 2009; 12 items (12 zines) (Box 19)
  - Madame Sata, 2014; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
  - Newsgirls, 2012; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
- Golden Collier Diasporan Savant Press zines, 2017-2018; 2018-S-0022, 2018-S-0072; 2 folders (2 folders)
  General
  Accession #2018-S-0022 includes the 2017 zines, Accession #2018-S-0072 includes the 2018 zines
  - Black Space, 2017; 2018-S-0022 (Box 19)
  - Musings on: Ancestors, 2017; 2018-S-0022 (Box 19)
  - Musings on: Black Womynhood, vol. 1, 2017; 2018-S-0022 (Box 19)
  - Musings on: Black Womanhood, vol. 2, 2017; 2018-S-0022 (Box 19)
  - when and where I enter: a nutritional womanist quotable, 2017; 2018-S-0022 (Box 19)
  - and then there were none: sanctuary, migration, gentrification, and the vanishing black metropolis, 2018; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
  - Black Banjo issue 1, 2018; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
  - Enough: Pan & Bi Sexual Erasure, 2018; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)
  - For the Godz: Legendary Houses of the Ballroom, 2018; 1 items (1 zine) (Box 19)